# Le Anh Nguyen

LinkedIn | GitHub | HackerRank

Location: Do Xuan Hop Street, 9 District, Ho Chi Minh City Email: nguyenla171120@gmail.com | Mobile: 0385-478-857

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled web developer with over 6 months of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript. I have knowledge of popular frameworks such as React.js, NodeJS, and Next.js and experience with REST APIs and improving performance of the website

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypescriptFrameworks: React.js, Express, Node.js, NextJSLibraries: Material, Redux, Tailwind, Sass

**Databases** : MongoDB, SQL Server

**Dev Tools** : Visual Studio Code, Github, Gitlab, Postman

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Frontend Developer Internship

August 2021 - October 2021

FPT Software

Fulltime – Ho Chi Minh City, 9 District, Viet Nam

- Learn about the workings of a system and build basic website interfaces as required through VueJS framework
- Learn some useful tools such as GitLab, nginx, IntelliJ, and fixed bugs of user interface
- Learn some software skills such as working with my team or talking with the leader how to correctly

## **Frontend Developer Fresher**

May 2022 - Nov 2022

HDWEBSOFT

Fulltime – Ho Chi Minh City, 9 District, Viet Nam

- Built user interface based on user interface design (figma) and get requirements from client
- Built UI through **NextJS** framework and **ChakraUI** library and also use **React-query** for some mini projects in company
- Coded with Web3 model UI such as Metamask, E-wallet for client and improve performance of product to better
- Integration with some websites and libraries to calculate and process payments, such as **Stripe**, **Google Analytics**, and **Paypal**

# **EDUCATION**

## **University of FPT**

Software engineering

An excellent student in August 2020 at FPT University

Ho Chi Minh City, 9 District, Viet Nam August 2018 – October 2022

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Portfolio Management**

React.js, Redux, Typescript, Material, Git

Source Code

- \* The project used to introduce myself through the website. This project has some specific features such as **overview information, pet project, experiences,** and some mini projects that I coded in the past
- Developed a clean and modern website using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript
- \* Optimized website for **speed and user experience**
- \* Utilized **responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- \* Deployed on Netlify pages

Youtube V3

Firebase, Material, React.js, Typescript

Source Code

- \* The website is based on a Youtube design. So this website has some signature features of social media websites including watching the list of videos by type, watching the content of the video, searching the video by title, and log in with google
- \* Developed a clean and modern website using Firesbase, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript